Can I talk to you, sir?
You are addicted to hard drugs.
Yes, man of God!
This is hard drugs
and you believe God can set you free.
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Hard drugs - he's addicted to hard drugs.
After taking it, he hears voices everywhere; there is a spirit tormenting him.
I'm his sister; I brought him here and whatever you said is very true.
He has been using drugs but that has always been the problem.
I've actually tried to help him.
I've not been able to so I brought him here for help.
Testimony Time
Jaspal Bharya
A Tanzanian Living In The UK
The man of God blessed me and I felt a very light relieving feeling.
He prophesied that I am addicted to hard drugs. The prophesy is definitely true.
When I was young, things that happened at my home really stressed me out.
On top of that, my education, homework and all that just piled up on me.
Smoking was an outlet for me.
I used to hide away from my parents and smoke.
I smoked cannabis.
When I went for further education in Birmingham, I continued smoking cannabis and hash as well.
It got to a point where I started selling my things for money to buy drugs.
I sold for instance, my mobile phone, my gold bracelet, my gold chain, and anything I could sell,
just to get money to buy drugs.
It got to a point where I could actually jump over fences to go and buy drugs.
I was a teenager, in high school when I started taking drugs,
and it was in 1994 when I went to Birmingham to do A-Levels.
I have been taking different kinds of drugs and that includes smoking, from 1994 until 2016.
That's approximately 22 years.
The drugs took over me and I was't my real self.
Basically, I lost my patience, I could not concentrate in my studies, I could not focus,
and I lose my temper for no reason. I was kind of confused too.
On a daily basis, how much of these drugs would you take?
It became like the way people have breakfast, and then lunch, and then dinner.
I was taking drugs in that way.
It was smoking which included; cannabis, hash, and cocaine. It really spoiled my health.
Non of my family members respected me - they looked down at me, downgraded me.
I felt really low within myself, deeply humiliated. I also felt responsible for all the problems in this world.
I did a lot of self harm to myself.
Haven't seen and experienced the bad things happening around me, affected me to take it out with drugs.
My father and my mother stopped giving me pocket money because I would spend it on drugs.
My parents got worried that if they give me money I would spend it on drugs,
and that would spoil my health.
My wife and children have separated from me because of drugs.
What efforts did you make on your own to get out of this drug addiction?
I tried the patches but it did not work. I tried the chewing gums as well, but I still smoked along side.
But when the man of God touched me I felt relieved, light and relaxed.
You said you tried so many things on the outside to stop this drug addiction.
Finally you came to The SCOAN.
Tell us how you found out about The SCOAN.
I found out from my father who has been here with my mother, my two younger brothers
and their wives and children.
Prophet T.B. Joshua gave you that prophesy and prayed for you.
What happened to you at that moment when he stretched his hand to pray for you?
When he touched my forehead, as you saw on the screen, I kind of woke up from my bubble.
That is the experience our brother is sharing. He said something just came out
as the Prophet prayed for him and gave him that prophecy in the power of the Holy Spirit.
Ever since the word of prophecy, what are the changes you have seen in your life?
I sleep a lot better, wake up a lot fresher, and I can breath a lot better.
What the man of God said is true and if it wasn't for him I wouldn't have felt this good.
Since you received that prophecy, have you taken any more of those drugs you were taking before?
Not at all. Since the prayer I have lost the urge and craving for any drug.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Brother, we believe you are in a position to give a word of advice to viewers all over the world,
especially those who may under the bondage of this kind of addiction.
What do you really want to advice them?
I advise people who are taking drugs to stop taking it,
and people who want to start taking drugs to not do it. It's not worth getting into it.
Smoking is highly addictive.
Smoking causes mucus and it makes your blood sticky.
That's just two of the negative things that come with it.
Thank you Jesus Christ. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ.
We know that the evidence of Jesus Christ is lives changed and our brother has taken a step in his
new life in Christ Jesus since that word of Prophecy last week,
and the deliverance he received from this drug addiction.
We pray that God will give him the grace to maintain his relationship with God
and we know that the best is yet to come in Jesus' name.